Guide to the Yale Peruvian Expedition Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Financial Records, 1911-1917; Series VII; 2' (5 boxes)
  - Expense books
    - Hardy, Hasbrouck, Maynard, 1914-1915 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Meserve, Westerberg, 1914-1915 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Record books, 1913, 1914 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Checkbook and stubs, 1914-1915 (Box 37, Folder 13-14)
  - Expense records
    - Bowman, Foote, Hendriksen, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Lanius, Tucker, Watkins, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Bestor, Bingham, 1912 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Bumstead, Eaton, Erdis, 1912 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Gregory, Hardy, Heald, 1912 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Little, Nelson, Rodriquez, Stephenson, 1912 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Expense record book, 1916 July-1917 August (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Work schedule records of staff assistants, 1913 June-December (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Time cards
    - Beckwith, 1913 November-December (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Bumstead, Albert H., 1914 April (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Erdis, Ellwood C., 1913 November-1914 April (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Hardy, Osgood, 1913 November-1914 April (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Small, 1913 November-1914 April (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Bills and receipts
    - 1911 February-1912 Dec, 1913-1914, undated (Box 39, Folder 26-46)
    - 1915-1917 May, undated (Box 40, Folder 47-56)
    - Yale University, 1913-1917 May (Box 40, Folder 57-61)
    - Eastman Kodak, 1911-1917 March (Box 40, Folder 62-63)
  - Ledger of expenses, 1911-1913 (Box 41, Folder 64)
- Additional material, 1912, 1916; Accession 2014-M-038
  - George F. Eaton's field journal, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    See also: series III, box 19, folder 18 (edited tyescript of notes).
  - The Collection of Osteological Material from Macchu Picchu, by George F. Eaton, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Volume, in poor condition, is inscribed "Julia H. Eaton/1916 from G.F.E."
- Additional material, 1911; Accession 2015-M-024
  This accession consists of materials produced by Herman Lathrop Tucker, who participated in the Yale Peruvian Expedition as the archaeological engineer. The materials consist of a typewritten letter written to his family, as well as photographs he took, both of which detail the ascent of the volcano Coropuna during the expedition.
  - Letter, 1911 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 2)